# Furkan Uzun

Bahçeşehir, Istanbul, 34488 +90 (545) 446 26 32 barisfurkanuz@gmail.com

Software developer with over 3 years of active experience in the field. Continually honed skills and expertise across various software domains. Designed numerous mobile applications, mobile games, and websites, demonstrating versatility and adaptability in tackling diverse projects. Worked on server-side programming languages and frameworks, database management, and API development

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ETIYA
Software Development Specialist

Hybrit, IST

December 2021-Present

- Develop REST and SOAP APIs with XML and Java Springboot
- Write XSL and XSLT transformations for API integration at middleware
- Implement message queueing systems with ActiveMQ for efficient communication between distributed components
- Develop order management (OM) processes with Camunda 7 and Camunda 8
- Manage the creation and orchestration of microservices using Docker and Kubernetes during the transition to a microservice architecture.
- Analyze and develop OpenAPIs
- Manage the creation and orchestration of microservices using Docker and Kubernetes during the transition to a microservice architecture
- Develop a user interface (UI) using Angular to enable developers and testers to track orders efficiently

CONNEXIO CLOUD Remote, NY

Game Developer, Level Designer, Frontend Developer

March 2022–August 2022

- Develop a website with JavaScript via React framework
- Utilize Figma to design and prototype website, ensuring effective user interface and experience design
- Develop a web3-compatible game using Unity via C#
- Develop AR and VR version of game

### **CARETTA SOFTWARE**

On-site, IST

Intern

July 2018–August 2018

- Get training about database structures and relations
- Develop customer relationship management (CRM) systems using C# via .NET framework

#### **EDUCATION**

#### ISTANBUL BILGI UNIVERSITY

IST

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Engineering

June 2021

Project: BilgiLife (GPA: 2,12)

a Unity 3D-developed application where students and prospective students can
explore and experience the campus in a virtual environment, modeled in Blender
and SketchUp.(The Project of Term Award)

### **PROJECTS**

# PERSONAL PORTFOLIO WEBSITE

IST

Software Developer March 2023

- Design the layout of the personal portfolio website using Figma
- Create the project structure using React and defining the basic components
- Style the components using CSS or CSS preprocessors to ensure design consistency
- Utilize React's state management and props to manage communication between components and data flow

# **CERTIFICATES**

TM FORUM

IST

November 2022

- Business Process Framework (eTOM)
- Information Framework(SID)
- Customer Centricity
- Open Digital Framework
- Open API

# ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Proficient in Java, C#, JavaScript, TypeScript, Dart, and CSS
- Experience in working with Spring Framework, React, and Node.js
- Proficient in effective and innovative UI/UX design
- Experience with best fit function in machine learning
- Fluent in English, basic knowledge of Italian and German

# **REFERENCES**

#### ERTAN ETLACAKUŞ

Senior Software Developer, Team Leader at ETIYA e.etlacakus@gmail.com

# **ALP DEMETGUL**

Senior Software Developer at Türkiye Halk Bankası A.Ş alpdemetgul@hotmail.com